

Syed Muhammad Saalain

Contact



+92 300 0580479







Skills

React Redux Persistence Routing

CSS/Canvas Animations

Firebase Firestore | Authentication

Git Github Object Oriented Programming

> MonaoDB NodeJS ExpressJS SocketIO

About me

I'm Saglain an ambitious problem solver with a passion for learning and implementing new solutions, and who would like to join a team of like-minded developers. Experienced in creating logical and innovative solutions to complex problems.

My goal is to climb the ladder and become one of the leading experts in my field, and want to be a part of something bigger.

Education

2019-Current

BS:SE University of Karachi

Intermediate Adamjee Govt Science College

Matriculation

Work Experience

2020 - Current

Slectus (US)

Multivendor ecommerce style platform with commision support and a complex profile and product management system and realtime features, MERN Stack App. Role: Frontend Developer, responsible for all the frontend work and integrations on the platform, little backend development authorized.

2020 - 2020

Novasoft

Software House.

Role: Frontend Developer, responsible for most of the frontend work and integrations on their multiple projects in works.

Al-Raheem Printing Services Role: Graphics Designer

3rd Party Projects

NFT-Crypto web gpps on ReactJS

Firebase Data and Auth applications Social Links sharing apps with NFC tag functionality

Many of my projects can be viewed on my webportfolio https://saalain1020.me

Extras

Fiverr freelancina experience

- Webicamp module winner
- Graphics desiging from Arena Multimedia
- Envoirment Modeling Workshop participation by Comstech of OIC